<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>playground on itsyuimorii</title>
    <link>https://itsyuimorii.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in playground on itsyuimorii</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:20:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://itsyuimorii.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The wind flows freely, may you do the same.</title>
      <link>https://itsyuimorii.com/posts/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:20:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyuimorii.com/posts/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description>Months turned into a year. But just as her collection grew, so did her lonliness. A pain as large as her heart lived in her chest. Nothing eased it. Not the Gulls, not a splendid sunset, not the rarest of shells. - Where the crawdads sing by Delia Owens
For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt like a stagnant pool, devoid of ripples, What am I steadfastly holding onto, what am I so fervently clinging to, even I myself do not understand.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Months turned into a year. But just as her collection grew, so did her lonliness. A pain as large as her heart lived in her chest. Nothing eased it. Not the Gulls, not a splendid sunset, not the rarest of shells.  &lt;em&gt;- Where the crawdads sing by Delia Owens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt like a stagnant pool, devoid of ripples, What am I steadfastly holding onto, what am I so fervently clinging to, even I myself do not understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I may appear gentle and reserved, silent as a calm, still pool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I am more than that—only I comprehend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only I know the true fervor and madness, the tumultuous waves roiling within! Like many ordinary, mundane individuals, I harbor both naive ideals and worldly desires—I am never content to settle!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I struggling to connect with my inner self.  Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ve magnified feelings of anxiety and helplessness. At times, I&amp;rsquo;ve even felt like drifting algae, following wherever the current takes me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have roots, but I flow.&amp;rdquo; - as Woolf said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I particularly resonate with Pessoa&amp;rsquo;s description of the self in &amp;ldquo;The Book of Disquiet,&amp;rdquo; it brings a sense of calm: &amp;ldquo;I am beginning to grasp the nature of my being. I do not truly exist.I am the chasm between the person I aspire to be and the impression others have crafted of me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am myself, unchanged,
me&amp;hellip;!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes, it is I, the embodiment of my own metamorphosis,
Regardless of what I am, or am not—it all coalesces into my essence.
Irrespective of my yearnings, or lack thereof—it shapes me.
Whether I cherish or disregard—it all stems from the same inner longing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am myself, exhaling deeply&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Perhaps, I am but a silent stream, flowing gently and steadily&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally, a quote from Camus:
&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I, I have no virtues. I have accepted myself. From then on, everything became simple.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;
Thankfully, even though I struggle to be loud, I connect with this world through the strokes of my brush and the notes of my music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://itsyuimorii.com/static/img/5B453925-DB3B-4622-BDB2-721A3AABCEF4.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;Hello Friend&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://itsyuimorii.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 23:16:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyuimorii.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello World Feeling as if the world is a farce was something I experienced when I first entered university. It&amp;rsquo;s a lonely cry of an idealist in the real world, often drowned out by the daytime hustle and bustle, only to find solace in the quiet of night. In those moments, discovering that one&amp;rsquo;s own voice can be heard, by oneself, brings joy and a sense of being moved. Yet, with the dawn, comes the inevitable return to reality.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling as if the world is a farce was something I experienced when I first entered university. It&amp;rsquo;s a lonely cry of an idealist in the real world, often drowned out by the daytime hustle and bustle, only to find solace in the quiet of night. In those moments, discovering that one&amp;rsquo;s own voice can be heard, by oneself, brings joy and a sense of being moved. Yet, with the dawn, comes the inevitable return to reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Idealists face the dilemma of being swept along by the currents of a world driven by interests, constantly questioning their actions&amp;rsquo; purpose, fluctuating between self-satisfaction from gains and despair from losses in the real world. They detest the reality they cannot change, unable to find a way to live independently and joyously from it. The saying goes, if you cannot detach from something or someone, it&amp;rsquo;s because you&amp;rsquo;re benefiting from it in some way, hence part of you is reluctant to let go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What then, should idealists strive for? A life detached from the material world, or a reluctant acceptance of reality? The former is hard due to competitive nature, desires, or basic survival needs, and the latter, while achievable, rarely brings happiness. Is there a middle path that allows for free movement between the ideal and the real world? Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s finding one&amp;rsquo;s ideal within reality – a mix of 80% pure passion and 20% interest. It means finding something you love that can also sustain you, but that&amp;rsquo;s immensely challenging. For instance, I love art, but how much can art earn me? And to link art with making money feels like a betrayal to both art and my passion, turning my life into a joke. Life, it seems, is much like a joke. If possible, let&amp;rsquo;s continue telling this joke until we can laugh it off in the end&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>playground</title>
      <link>https://itsyuimorii.com/playground/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyuimorii.com/playground/</guid>
      <description></description>
      <content></content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://itsyuimorii.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyuimorii.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World 元気でいますか? 大事な人はできましたか? いつか夢は叶いますか?</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;元気でいますか?
大事な人はできましたか?
いつか夢は叶いますか?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;https://itsyuimorii.com/img/me.jpg&#34;  alt=&#34;Hello Friend&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  style=&#34;border-radius: 8px;&#34;    /&gt;


</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
