<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self-Discovery on itsyuimorii</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/self-discovery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self-Discovery on itsyuimorii</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:20:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/self-discovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Second Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:20:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description>The wind is free, I hope you too.
Months turned into a year. But just as her collection grew, so did her lonliness. A pain as large as her heart lived in her chest. Nothing eased it. Not the Gulls, not a splendid sunset, not the rarest of shells. - Where the crawdads sing by Delia Owens
For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt like a stagnant pool, devoid of ripples, struggling to connect with my inner self.</description>
      <content>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wind is free, I hope you too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Months turned into a year. But just as her collection grew, so did her lonliness. A pain as large as her heart lived in her chest. Nothing eased it. Not the Gulls, not a splendid sunset, not the rarest of shells.  &lt;em&gt;- Where the crawdads sing by Delia Owens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt like a stagnant pool, devoid of ripples, struggling to connect with my inner self. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ve magnified feelings of anxiety and helplessness. At times, I&amp;rsquo;ve even felt like drifting algae, following wherever the current takes me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have roots, but I flow.&amp;rdquo; - as Woolf said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I particularly resonate with Pessoa&amp;rsquo;s description of the self in &amp;ldquo;The Book of Disquiet,&amp;rdquo; it brings a sense of calm: &amp;ldquo;I am beginning to grasp the nature of my being. I do not truly exist.I am the chasm between the person I aspire to be and the impression others have crafted of me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am myself, unchanged,
me&amp;hellip;!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes, it is I, the embodiment of my own metamorphosis,
Regardless of what I am, or am not—it all coalesces into my essence.
Irrespective of my yearnings, or lack thereof—it shapes me.
Whether I cherish or disregard—it all stems from the same inner longing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am myself, exhaling deeply&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Perhaps, I am but a silent stream, flowing gently and steadily&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;/And finally, a quote from Camus:
&amp;ldquo;I, I have no virtues. I have accepted myself. From then on, everything became simple.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Hello Friend&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/static/img/5B453925-DB3B-4622-BDB2-721A3AABCEF4.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
