<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Momery on itsyuimorii</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/momery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Momery on itsyuimorii</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:21:03 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/momery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time&#39;s Tapestry - A Journey of Resilience and Renewal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:21:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/second/</guid>
      <description></description>
      <content></content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Marnie Was There 思い出のマーニー(2014)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 14:21:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>When Marnie was There When Marnie was There is a movie from Studio Ghibli, directed by Hiromasa Yonebayashi, based on the novel of the same name by Joan G. Robinson. 🎬 It was released in Japan on July 19, 2014. It is the last film produced by Studio Ghibli before its temporary closure in 2014. It`s a movie being underrated and lesser-known from Studio Ghibli.
When I saw Marnie start waving to Anna Sasaki(あんな), I could no longer stop my tears.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;when-marnie-was-there&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/&#34;&gt;When Marnie was There&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Marnie was There is a movie from Studio Ghibli, directed by Hiromasa Yonebayashi, based on the novel of the same name by Joan G. Robinson. 🎬 It was released in Japan on July 19, 2014. It is the last film produced by Studio Ghibli before its temporary closure in 2014. It`s a movie being underrated and lesser-known from Studio Ghibli.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I saw Marnie start waving to Anna Sasaki(あんな), I could no longer stop my tears. Marnie&amp;rsquo;s childhood was anything but happy, abused, her hus-band died early and even her only daughter didn&amp;rsquo;t want her until her daughter died in a car accident. Anna, her granddaughter, became her only relative, and she gave her all her love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My heart broke when Anna, who did not know the truth, said that she would not forgive her parents and grandmother for leaving her alone. The film uses another wonderful narrative to resolve Anna&amp;rsquo;s inner brokenness, as Marnie asks her for forgiveness for leaving her in the silo (a metaphor for when she died too young to grow up with her beloved granddaughter). In the end, Anna says, &amp;ldquo;Of course I forgive you. I love you&amp;rdquo;, you can see the great happiness and relief on Marnie&amp;rsquo;s face as she knows that her beloved granddaughter has forgiven her. What a beautiful bittersweet story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was an overwhelming, beautiful film that conveyed a beautiful message that -&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt; &amp;#34;The person who loves you may leave one day, but his/her love will always be there.&amp;#34;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;soundtrack&#34;&gt;Soundtrack&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wbuOD2ijXL0&amp;ab_channel=mintleaf1993&#34;&gt;I am not alone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kbK3Uwf-cOw&amp;ab_channel=kwazimouto&#34;&gt;Find on the Outside&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mpivDxXr0IM&amp;ab_channel=Blueberry&#34;&gt;Deep inside my heart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
